

# **EDUCATION**

#### **BCA**

Tilak Maharashtra University, Pune. 2007-2010

#### **HIGHER SECONDARY SCHOOL**

Maharashtra State Board 2005-2007

#### SECONDARY SCHOOL

Maharashtra State Board 2004-2005

### CONTACT

#### **Address**

Flat 501, 5th floor, Bhosale Heights, Dhayari, Pune-411041.

#### **Phone**

+91 9730944344

#### **Email**

abhijitdaphale@gmail.com

# **TECHNICAL SKILL**

HTML 5

CSS3 / SASS

Javascript

Jquery

Bootstrap

**Angular** 

Adobe Photoshop / Xd

# **ABHIJIT DAPHALE**

WEB UI DEVELOPER

### **ABOUT ME**

Sr. Front End Developer with around 8 years of extensive experience in the field of Web Applications development using HTML 5, CSS 3, JavaScript, jQuery, Angular, Apex Chart, XHTML, AJAX, JSON, Bootstrap 5.2 and Responsive Web Design, Browser Testing and Debugging, Proficient in developing web page quickly and effectively using, HTML 5, CSS3 and also experience in making webpage cross-browser compatible.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **UI DEVELOPER**

Appcart Systems Pvt Ltd, Pune.

July 2018 - Present

- Web design and development, application evelopment musing HTML5, CSS3, SASS, Javascript, Jquery, Angular, Ionic v1 and vs code.
- Designing the dynamic and multi-browser compatible pages using HTML5, CSS3, and Angular.
- Worked on Google Maps, Apex chart, High Chart library.
- Integrating the front end using the JSON data from the backend mainly PHP API calls.
- Working closely with the backend team.
- Developing the users application by editing updating using MVC pattern in Angular.
- Developing the various pages and its architecture in accordance with to UI specs.

#### **HTML DEVELOPER**

Olive Design and Communication Pvt Ltd, Pune.

Sept 2014 - June 2018

- Web design and development, application development using Photoshop, HTML, Javascript, and Dreamweaver.
- Designed dynamic and multi-browser compatible pages using html, css, angular js and javascript.
- Creating cross-browser compatible CSS-based layouts.
- Participated in bug thrashing sessions to discuss and resolve
- Responsible for creating the screens with table-less designs meeting w3c standards

# **LANGUAGES**

English		
Hindi		
Marathi		

# **WORK SUMMERY**

WEB APPLICATIONS			
Name	HAWKEYE		
Technology	HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, Javascript, Bootstrap 5, Angular11.		
Roll	Design and Creating Components Library		
Description	HawkEye is a Centralized Security Management system.		
Responsibility	<ul> <li>Creating component as per providing style guide from UX team.</li> <li>Using HTML, CSS3 and Bootstrap.</li> </ul>		
	• Connect with the UX team and verify the created components.		
	• Using Scss creating Light theme and Dark theme.		
Name	HR NEETI		
Technology	HTML5, CSS3, Jquery, Javascript, Bootstrap, Angular.		
Roll	Design and Development		
Description	HR Neeti's software is one of the most comprehensive HCMS, simplifying employee lifecycle management, workforce planning, performance management, rewards and more with in-depth features designed to drive business growth.		
Responsibility	<ul> <li>Creating efficient design and developing User Interaction screens using HTML, CSS3, Bootstrap, JavaScript, Angular4.</li> </ul>		
	<ul> <li>Enhanced application performance by Angular 6</li> <li>Component based development in view of future Angular framework transitions.</li> </ul>		
	• Implemented Angular Router to enable navigation from one view to the next as customer performs application tasks.		
	<ul> <li>Used AJAX, JSON to send request to the server to check the functionality of the websites and for storing and exchanging information between browsers and servers.</li> </ul>		
Name	FINSTATRACK		
Technology	HTML5, CSS3, Jquery, Javascript, Bootstrap, Reactjs.		
Roll	Design and Development		
Description	■ Take an Assessment - Assess your company against		

Description

- Take an Assessment Assess your company against standard revenue and cost parameters.
- Track your Growth Has your performance improved or deteriorated over time?
- Compare How do you fare against your peers, competitors, and other Cloud & SaaS companies worldwide? Track your performance against benchmarks and see your company ranking on the leaderboard!
- My Assessment View your current assessment in a graphical format. View previous assessments and previous leaderboard rankings!

- **Responsibility** Deal with front end pages that were created in an expert way utilizing HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Reactjs
  - Making cross-program perfect and models consistent CSS-based page formats.
  - Created responsive UI structure for advanced mobile phone, iPad, and tablet screen.
  - Develop with react Functional based approach.

# **WORK SUMMERY**

#### **MOBILE APPLICATIONS**

Name PATANKAR HOSPITAL

Technology HTML5, CSS3, Ionic v1 and JavaScript.

Roll Design and Developed Application.

**Description** It is a personal mobile application for doctors to view the daily, weekly updates of appointments, operation, OPD etc.

Responsibility • Developed re

• Developed responsive UI design for smart phone, iPad, and tablet using Ionic 1.

 Worked on front end that was developed in a professional manner using HTML, CSS and JavaScript.

 Participated in bug thrashing sessions to discuss and resolve bugs with developers.

Name MOTARYAH

Technology Ionic 5 and Angular

**Roll** Bugs Fixing and adding new functionality.

**Description** Motaryah is an application that will list all cars/motorbikes shops based on their type of provided services and we will offer

you two main types of services, either on concierge or on the spot to let you focus on whatever you do in life while we take

care of your car/motorbike.

Name CITYXONES

**Technology** HTML5, CSS3, PhoneGap, Cordova, Esri's GIS mapping software

**Roll** Design, Developed and Deploy.the application.

**Description** Local and community platform. Hyperlocal news and information.

Responsibility • Developed responsive UI design for smart phone, iPad, and

tablet using PhoneGap and Cordova.

 Worked on front end that was developed in a professional manner using HTML, CSS and JavaScript, Map plugins using Esri's map.

 Participated in bug thrashing sessions to discuss and resolve bugs with developers.

Name CARTERA EVENTS

**Technology** HTML5, CSS3, PhoneGap, Cordova, Esri's GIS mapping software

**Roll** Design, Developed and Deploy.the application.

 $\textbf{Description} \qquad \text{Local and community platform. Hyperlocal news and information.}$ 

Responsibility • Developed responsive UI design for smart phone, iPad, and tablet using PhoneGap and Cordova.

 Worked on front end that was developed in a professional manner using HTML, CSS and JavaScript, Map plugins using Esri's map.

 Participated in bug thrashing sessions to discuss and resolve bugs with developers.

# **WORK SUMMERY**

### **OTHER PROJECTS**

- http://amolbapat.com/
- http://projectibdaa.com/
- http://www.dukkanonline.ae/ (Admin and Website)
- http://kabat.ae/ (Admin and Website)
- https://services.deltachannels.com/recruiter/coverage-mode
- https://services.deltachannels.com/generic/recruiter-auto-lo
- http://www.patankarfertilitysolutions.com
- http://www.patankarhospital.com
- http://www.dviewcctv.com
- http://appcartsystems.com/

М	a	ny	m	OI	re	
141	а	пy		0	C	١

I hereby declare that all the above-mentioned	information	provided l	by me i	s correct
and true to the best of my knowledge and be	ief.			

Date:	Yours Truly,
Place:	Abhijit Daphale